Upcami
It's time for another episode of "Upokami".  This time we will be talking with Kamiko Claire Moe of Angulum and Yoshio Sate of Bey once Shusenings.
This is a program that takes you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the up-front group.
We will show you the process of recording and rehearsal.
First of all, let me tell you about the behind-the-scenes of our two MCs.
First of all, I, Kuriho Kamiko, am a new member of Angeleum with Yukiho and Hana Gotoh on the lower board,
We started rehearsals with 51 members.
It was only the fifth time I met them,
The atmosphere was really bright all the time,
The air was really bright and sparkling.
I was sure they were nervous when they joined the song, but they were trying their best,
Angstrom is a cheerful group to begin with,
I really feel that the brightness of Angelem has been improved to another level.
I feel that the brightness of Angelem has been further improved,
I am really looking forward to the future of Angulum.
Beyonce has not had the experience of welcoming new members yet,
That's right.
It's not easy to get that kind of atmosphere in a fresh way,
I thought it was wonderful,
It had been about a year and a half since we had a new member,
It had been about a year and a half since we had a new member, so it had been a long time since I had felt that way.
I am really looking forward to the summer tour.
I will do my best.
I, Yoshi Satoh, performed at the Nippon Budokan in May,
In May alone, we performed four patterns of "Megane no Shonen no Shonen" (Boy with Glasses), our debut single.
There were 2 patterns for the spring tour, the original version, and the Budokan version,
All of them were set in parallel worlds,
The same person, but with different friends and different personalities,
When I got the script at first, I was so excited that I wanted to do it,
When I first received the script, I thought, "What am I going to do?
Isn't it hard? I was worried that I would have to memorize 4 patterns.
I was quite anxious,
But the moment I realized that all the characters were different from each other, I thought I might be able to do it,
I thought I might be able to do something.
I could do it with different senses,
But we all agreed on the lines in the dressing room right before the performance,But we all worked hard in the backstage to make sure we got the lines together right before the show,
We all worked very hard to complete the four patterns.
I think we were able to do that because the members of the group don't change,
I think that's because there is no turnover in the members.
I would also like to try switching places in Ange.
Depending on the song.
I hope we can do that in various ways.
Now, let's start with this time's Up-Kami.
Juice-Juice Pride Bright Making of Music Video Shooting
Juice-Juice's latest single was released on July 12.
Please take a look at the making of the music video for "Pride Bright," Juice-Juice's newest single, which was released on July 12.
We filmed the chorus together this time, didn't we?
Indeed.
So please listen to it and pay attention to the chorus.
Bye-bye!
I'm a strong woman. Today.
Thank you for listening.
Bright Bride" has very feminine lyrics or something like that, so it's a song about being weak but strong, so I've been thinking about how to express that.
Bright Bride has very feminine lyrics or something like that, so I've been thinking about how to express that.
I just finished shooting the lip scene.
The lyrics are a bit difficult to write.
I'm trying to express the complicated feelings of a girl.
She's a little bossy, but she's a weak girl.
I'm hoping I can express that.
I hope I can express that.
It's very difficult to do so with just facial expressions.
I'm going to try to do my best today.
I'm going to try my best.
The camera's V moves.
I'm going to try to make it quicker.
So it's a little bit like a dubbed sound.
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't love you, so I'm not going to kiss you before the extension, but I'm not going to kiss you before the extension, but I'm going to kiss you again, completely, so I couldn't take you.
Now we're going to a room I've never seen before.
I'm going to go to a room I've never seen before, and this time I hear it's full of mannequins.
I saw the mannequins before entering the studio.
There were quite a few mannequins.There were quite a lot of mannequins there.
I'm looking forward to seeing them in the show!
Let's go!
One, two, three, four, seven, eight.
slippers
me
ni
ahhh ahhh ahhh ahhh
I'm not kissing you. I'm flapping my wings.
I wanted to tell you
At that time...
I'm a shagamonger, so I think this song is a little different from the previous ones in terms of the intensity of the movements.
I think this song has a different intensity from the previous ones, so I think it is a little difficult.
The set also has a lot of mannequins and stylish lights, so it's a fresh feeling again.
Are you looking forward to it?
Yes, I am. It was good.
Number one in the list of people who say "No, no, no, no!
No, no, no. Look forward.
Even you couldn't give it to me.
Yes, please get up.
I beg you
BABYMETAL
Oh!
♪ BABYMETAL
Yes, sir
Yes, sir. Good work.
Well, let's go wait for the recording, shall we?
Yes, please wait
Okay, thank you for your hard work.
Yes, thank you.
I was so young.
I wanted to love. I couldn't.
No planned kisses.
You couldn't even take me away from you.You couldn't even take it away from me.
Pride, pride, pride
Only one and No. 1
No, no, no, look forward
Even you couldn't give it to mePride.
Good night.
Pan-pan-pan, Carica Kiddo
Only one & only one I'm a review
I wanted to love, I wanted to be loved
I would not despair or hurt
If I was born to be a flower
All around you look back
Only one & only one
Thank you
Filming is over.
Thank you for your hard work!
So, we've just finished shooting a music video!
I'm really excited about it.
I thought the day was very intense this time, too.
I was so excited to dance as hard as I could, and to really put my heart into it as many times as I could.
The teacher was passionate about using the best dancers.
Everyone was so passionate about making us dance in a cool way.
But the choreography was a little bit sticky.
It's a little scary.
Maybe I'm afraid of women.
I felt that there was a lot of femininity in the simplicity of the dance.
I felt that there was a lot of femininity in the simplicity.
I think I was able to express that kind of strength and tenacity.
I think the song is perceived in different ways.
I'm really looking forward to seeing how everyone will react to it!
And personally, I like it this way.
My hair is different from the usual, and it's different from my straight hair.
I had my hair done in a fresh new way.
I want to give everyone a new look.
I'm sure each and every one of you will be able to find it.I'm sure each and every one of you will find out.
I hope you're looking forward to it!
I'm looking forward to it.
Bye bye!
Yes, I saw it, how did you like it? Well, from the lip scene, it was like a switch was turned on, including the recent additions, Sakaya Ishiyama and Akari Endo.You know, their expressions...
I thought it was wonderful that JuiceJuice's atmosphere or color came out from the lip scene of each of them.
I think JuiceJuice has a lot of mature and relaxed songs, and you can see that in the making of the show, but behind the scenes, they're playing with each other.
I thought how adorable she was, and I was able to see so many wonderful sides of her.
That's all for the making of JuiceJuice's Pride Bright music video shoot.
I wanted to love you, but I couldn't.
I wouldn't kiss you on the level
Even you couldn't take it away from me
JuiceJuice Pride Bright
Now on sale
Don't be too hard on yourself.
Here is the next one. Angulum Ai no Kedamono Vocal Recording
Here's a look at the vocal recording of Akari Takeuchi, from the latest single by Angelem, "Ai no Kedamono"!
Okay, so is there anything you don't understand? No problem!
Okay, let's start filming!
Let's start with the emblem.
From "I like poison" to "That's not all there is to it.
Yes, sir.
People ask me if I like Doc, but in the end, it's not a gut feeling.
Mikami's so distressed that she backs away. Love is not that big a deal.
That's what I meant. I'll go shoot another one.
Okay.
People ask me what I like about him, but in the end, it's not a gut feeling.
It's not the kind of love that makes you withdraw after three days and three nights.
OK!
We are Gao will do this later, so please do Life for Love or Life on the Line first.
That's not the extent of love
I'm not going to hide it anymore. You're the target.
You're the target.
You can talk to your target right now, but...So, you can talk to your target right now, but...
Target.
Okay, let's try this again.
That's not what love is all about.
You're the target.
You're my target, you're my target
Okay, let's go to the B melody.It must be beautiful. I can't hold back.
I can't be shy.
BGM.
OK!
Yes!
Yes! Let's go to the chorus!
BGM
I love you, but we are like this
Even a lonely boy genius
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
Aishitare, aishitare, aishitare, aishitare, aishitare, aishitare, yes
Okay, let's do six shots like that.
Now jump out of the car
I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you, I love you
If we arrive, if we feel it, if our eyes meet
We who love and are deeply moved
We're lonely and sensitive boys
Yes, OK
Then let's go, love
Yes, yes
Someone we want to love
Burning encounters are on the verge of extinction
Someone who wants to love you
I'll protect you so much, won't I?
Yeah, that's how it is.
If we love each other, we can be brave and strong, can't we?
Yes.
And after that, the earth comes in from a little low place to begin with,
I hope we can come in as good as the person who sang before us.I hope I can come in feeling as good as the person who sang before me.
Yes.
Let's try one more time.
I want to love you, heart, we
Burning encounters are on the verge of extinction
Loneliness. From now on, too.I'll protect you, right?
Okay, okay.
Okay, let's continue.
I'll protect you so much, won't I?
I'm going to protect you so much...
I'm gonna protect you so much...
I'll protect you so much, won't I?
You're a loser at love... be prepared
You did a great job recording your vocals.
Amazing.
I didn't realize it was so easy to finish.
I knew you were good, but...
I thought it was amazing.
It was amazing.
I don't have the words.
How was it?
Well...
It's a lot of words.
You have to have a good rhythm.
I thought it would be difficult to make out the words.
But you don't really need subtitles.
You can hear it so well.
It's amazing how clearly I can hear the words.
There are a lot of songs that have a lot of words in them.
But if you're really conscious of it, you can get used to the rhythm.
Yes, it's difficult, isn't it?
I thought it was really difficult to balance the two.I thought it would be really difficult to balance that.
It was amazing.
Once again, I felt that Ms. Takeuchi is an amazing senior.
That's all for the vocal recording by Akari Takeuchi of Angulum: Ai no Kedamono!
Let's take it easy today.
With Yuu Kamiokura of Angulum
Beyonce and Seasonings' Yoshi Sato and Utano are here with Upokami.
Next up is
Beyonce, Choral Recording for "Yozora no Yume wo Yawagurenai Yozora ni" ("I Can't Even Draw a Dream")From Beyonce's latest single
I can't even draw a dream in the night sky
Beyonce members recorded the song.
Hello. Nice to meet you.
Today, I'd like to take some pictures of the chorus part.
The three main singers. We're going to sing together.
We'll start with the intro part.
I can't even sing about love.
We'll shoot this part.
The image is already a chorus, so it's like a high school chorus that's going to compete in the national chorus contest.
You can think of us as a school that's strong enough to compete in the National Chorus Gonkour, and I'd like the three of us to deliver beautiful harmonies in perfect harmony.
I hope you can enjoy the beautiful harmony of the three of us.
I won't let the night sky where even love can't be sung
It's wonderful that you were born as you are
Yes, it's perfect. You're breathing perfectly.
Let's go to number 2.
It's "La la la la," the 2A part.
Yes, perfect.
La la la la.
Yes, ok. Hello?
Yes, it's the part about the litt.
The part where the tempo gets slower and slower, I'd like to make it a little like my otzuki.
I'd like to do it like my otzuki.
I can't even sing about love
It's wonderful!
Yes, it's OK.Yes, OK.
Cute.
Hey, I thought
Yes, the most second part
The hardest part is the last bit
The tempo gets slower and slower
the tempo gets slower and slower.
I think the timing here is a little difficult.
Listen to the piano.Listen to the piano.
I hope you can get the timing right.
Let's walk while humming the melody
I can't even sing about love
As you won't let me
Woo, it's beautiful!
Yes, I think I got it.
Yes, hello?
Hello?
Nice to meet you.
Yes, please.
Let's go for the first bass part.
Yes, sir.
Let's walk while singing your favorite melody.
I can't even sing about love
I won't let you
It's beautiful.
Yes, it's okay.
Hello?
Yes, ma'am.
Here you go.
Now for the treble team.
Yes, sir.
I'd like to play this third one.
It's a big band or something like that.It's a genre of music called "big band.
So, earlier it was like a chorus, but here it's more like a chorus soulful.
But here it's more like a soulful chorus.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's going to be tight.
I hope so.
I can't even sing about love
As you won't let me
I don't know about anyone else.
Even now.
Uh Uh Uh Uh UhAh, my dreams don't even follow
In the blink of an eye
Uh Uh Uh Uh Uh Uh
Okay, okay. One second.
Now for the third one...
Yes, this one...
Let's do it in your own voice.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
No one's going to mess it up. Watch over us.
Uh Uh Uh Uh Uh Ah
Uh uh uh uh Uh uh
Uh Uh Uh Uh
It's too bad. Let's start with "Even in a dream". Even a dream will come true. Uh Uh Uh
Even dreams don't come true.
Is it okay? The moment
Uh Uh Uh
Yes, I think I got it.
Hello?
Yes, ma'am.
Here you go.
You must be the bass team.
Yes, sir.
Very fine phrasing.
This is more of a back chorus.
Yes, please make it rather strong.Yeah, you have to make it rather strong.
And the 16th beat is coming in.
I want the rhythm to be tight.
I'd like you to do it.
No one can mess with it. Watch over us.
Uh Uh Uh Uh Ah
Even in my dreams, it's not possible, the moment I'm here
Uh Uh Uh Uh
Yes, it's perfect. That's all.
Yes, thank you for your time. Thank you very much.I had a chance to see the no-kill recording chorus.
It was interesting.
I'm glad.
I would like to see such a variety of parts, sometimes low-pitched, sometimes high-pitched.
It sounds like a lot of work.
Yes, it is.
This song has a chorus part for the first time ever,
There is also a brass band arrangement,
The song has a brass band arrangement, so it is a very layered song overall,
The chorus part was chosen to add warmth to the lyrics as well,
I'm glad about that.
I saw this song at the Nippon Budokan concert,
I saw this song at the Nippon Budokan, and it brought tears to my eyes.
It was such a wonderful song, so I am glad.
I am very happy.
This is Beyonce's chorus recording of "In the Night Sky I Can't Even Draw a Dream.
Maybe it's the summer, maybe it's a dream, maybe I'm a little emotionally unstable
Onogawa Gentle glue
Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer July 26 release
It's going to be good.
It's time to say goodbye to the up-dated paper that Shinkyoku Ryozen and Riyo Uta have been sending you!
We've seen a lot of different videos this time.
I, Riho, was watching the making of Juice Juice's "Pride Bright.
I was watching the making-of video of Juice Juice's Pride Bright, and I was impressed by the way they filmed each phrase.
I was also impressed by that.
I thought the music video really showed Juice Juice's group color.I thought that Juice Juice's group color really came out in this music video.
Yes, I, Shinkyoku Ling, was also impressed by Beyonce's chorus vocal recording.
I was amazed at the way they recorded the vocals.
I love many of Beyonce's songs.
I'm so happy!
I'm really glad I got to see it.
In Up Paper, we will be going behind the scenes of the production of various artists who belong to the Up Front Group.
Please subscribe to our channel to get a glimpse of what you don't normally see!
In this edition of Upshi, we'll be talking with Shinkyoku Ryomai of Angulum and
and Yoshio Sota of Beyonce Seasonings.
Good bye!
Next time on Up-Kami
Juice-Juice Funky Flash InnThe making of music video shooting
And
We will also be showing the recording of Angulum Mobile Sousei!
Please look forward to it!
Thank you for watching!